Inside Albany Records
Inside Albany Records
1975-2006
Inside Albany, Inc.
141 linear ft.
Broadcast master videorecordings and program files for the weekly television news show Inside Albany.
2534125
Biographical History
Inside Albany was New York's leading weekly television news magazine focusing on the contemporary events and issues of New York State government and politics. Produced by Public Television Station WMHT-TV (Schenectady), the program aired from January 2, 1975 to December 29, 2006. Originally a one-hour weekly program, Inside Albany was later condensed to a half-hour format. Inside Albany has won numerous broadcasting awards including the Alfred I. duPont-Columbia University Award for excellence in television journalism.
David Hepp was a founding producer and reporter for Inside Albany. Lise Bang-Jensen started with the program in 1987 as reporter-producer and co-host. Mr. Hepp is a graduate of Syracuse University's Newhouse School of Public Communications.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Inside Albany Records consist of program files and videorecordings relating to the television program Inside Albany.
Program files contains program notes and descriptions of shows from 1975-2006, three binders listing show topics from 1985-2006, and a zip drive containing a name library and lists of show topics from 1987-2006, in AppleWorks format. Videorecordings contain recordings of of televised Inside Albany programs, including several specials (1975-2006). Episodes 1144 through 1146 (4/19/85-5/3/85), 2109 through 2112 (8/4/94-8/25/94), and 2114 (9/8/94) are not present in the collection.
According to documentation received with the material, the program numbering system followed July-June fiscal year beginning in July 1976. In the first year, production was suspended in July when the legislative session recessed and resumed when it reconvened in September with program No. 201. After Inside Albany became an independent production in January 1996, the program numbering system was changed to be based on the calendar year, thus the first program in January 1996 was No. 9601.
At over 1,600 episodes on over 750 videotapes, the collection documents a wide range of events and figures including the Love Canal cleanup, the Attica prison riots, the Shoreham nuclear power plant shutdown, the political careers of Mario Cuomo, George Pataki, Eliot Spitzer, Hillary Clinton, as well as important social issues, like Native American rights, disability rights, and many others.
Other Formats Available
Broadcast master videotapes have been digitized. Each episode has been converted to a low-resolution access file (.mp4) for web streaming, and a high-resolution preservation file (.mov). In addition, each original tape and tape container has been photographed. All episodes are available on campus via.
Arrangement of the Collection
Program files remain in the order they were received. Videorecordings are listed in order by show number (see Scope and Content above).
Boxes 92 through Box 95 are shelved with the collection but not strictly speaking part of it. These contain hard drives holding the digital master files, created by as part of the digitization process.
Related Material
has a number of television-related collections. Please refer to for a complete listing
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Politics, government and public administration; New York State; Inside Albany, Inc.; WMHT (Television station: Schenectady, N.Y.); Inside Albany (television show); Broadcast journalism.; Public television -- New York (State); Television broadcasting of news -- United States.; Television in politics -- New York (State); New York (State) -- Politics and government.; Born digital.; Digital moving image formats.; Files (document groupings); Videotapes.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
The AppleWorks database is not accessible due to technical difficulties.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Inside Albany, Inc. and WMHT-TV (Schenectady).
Inventory
- Program files
  - Index card files, A-K, 2 card files (Box 96)
    Index card files for various people who appeared on the show. Each card lists a person, and then the date(s) and episode number(s) on which they appeared. A quick survey of the files indicates that the information appears to span the mid-1980s to the mid-2000s. Cards are filed in alphabetical order by surname of person.
  - Index card files, L-Z, 3 card files (Box 97)
  - Program files, 1975-1976 (Box 98)
    [no number given] (1/3/75)
    [no number given] (1/10/75)
    No. 201 (9/4/75) to No. 222 (1/29/76)
    There are no program folders for No. 2 (1/16/75) through No. 28 (7/10/75)
  - Program files, 1976 (Box 99)
    No. 223 (2/5/76) to No. 243 (6/26/76)
    Welfare special (no date given)
  - Program files, 1976-1978 (Box 79)
    Composite list 1st programming year
    List of those people appearing on Inside Albany for second programming year
    List of those on third programming year
    4th year list DVPs
    No. 301 (7/3/76) to No. 348 (5/26/77)
    Constitutional Ball Special (5/27/77)
    No. 349 (6/3/77) to No. 352 (6/23/77)
    No. 401 (6/30/77) to No. 452 (6/23/78)
  - Program files, 1978-1981 (Box 80)
    List of those people appearing on fourth year
    No. 501 (6/30/78) to No. 531 (1/26/79)
    Recollections of Rockefeller Special (1/29/79)
    No. 532 (2/2/79) to No. 552 (6/22/79)
    No. 601 (6/29/79) to No. 652 (6/27/80)
    No. 701 (6/27/80) to No. 749 (5/30/81)
    Casino gambling special (6/3/81)
    No. 750 (6/6/81) to No. 752 (6/20/81)
    There are no program folders for Nos. 610, 628, 631-633
  - Program files, 1981-1983 (Box 81)
    No. 801 (6/27/81) to No. 820 (11/7/81)
    Election 81: Prisons and Jobs (Nov 81)
    No. 821 () to No. 852 (6/18/82)
    Conventions(includes booklet from New York State Democratic Committee)
    No. 901 (6/25/82) to No. 952 (6/17/83)
  - Program files, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    No. 1001 (6/24/83) to No. 1035 (2/7/84)
    Black & P.R. Caucus, 13th (1984)
    No. 1036 (2/24/84) to No. 1052 (6/15/84)
    No. 1101 (6/22/84) to No. 1152 (6/15/85)
  - Program files, 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    No. 1201 (6/21/85) to No. 1231 (1/17/86)
    Black & P.R. Weekend
    No. 1232 (1/24/86) to No. 1252 (6/13/89)
    No. 1301 (6/20/86) to No. 1328 (12/24/86)
  - Program files, 1987-1988 (Box 84)
    No. 1329 (1/3/87) to No. (6/12/87)
    No. 1401 (6/20/87) to No. 1403 (7/3/87)
    Black & P.R. Caucus
    No. 1404 (7/10/87) to No. 1437 (2/27/88)
    Black & P.R. Caucus W'end
    No. 1438 (3/4/88) to No. 1452 (6/11/88)
    No. 1501 (6/16/88) to No. 1529 (12/30/88)
  - Program files, 1989-1991 (Box 85)
    No. 1530 (1/6/89) to No. 1829 (12/27/91)
  - Program files, 1992-1994 (Box 86)
    No. 1830 (1/4/92) to No. 2052 (6/3/94)
  - Program files, 1994-1997 (Box 87)
    No. 2101 (6/9/94) to No. 9726 (6/27/97)
    Last show with public television was No. 2207 (6/27/97), resumed production as independent with No. 9601 (1/6/96)
  - Program files, 1997-1999 (Box 88)
    No. 9727 (7/4/97) to No. 9952 (12/24/99)
  - Program files, 2000-2003 (Box 89)
    No. 0001 (1/1/00) to No. 0326 (6/27/03)
  - Program files, 2003-2006 (Box 90)
    No. 0327 (7/4/03) to No. 0652 (12/29/06)
  - Show topics, 1985-2006; 3 binders (Box 91)
  - Inside Albany Name Library, Pataki Library, 1987-2006; AppleWorks file on magnetic disk (ZIP disk) (Box 91)
    This item is not currently accessible.
- Videorecordings
  All episodes have been digitized and are available on campus via.
  - Videorecordings, 1975
    - No. 1, 1975-01-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0001; originally misidentified as episode 2 (Box 1)
    - [No. 2], 1975-01-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0002; no show no. on slate; inferred as no. 2 based on date (Box 1)
    - [No. 3], 1975-01-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0003; show misnumbered as no. 4 on slate; inferred as no. 3 based on date (Box 1)
    - [No. 4], 1975-01-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0004; show misnumbered as no. 5 on slate; inferred as no. 4 based on date (Box 1)
    - [No. 5], 1975-02-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0005; no show no. on slate; inferred as no. 5 based on date (Box 1)
    - No. 6, 1975-02-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0006; originally misidentified as episode 7 (Box 1)
    - No. 7, 1975-02-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0015; originally misidentified as episode 16 (Box 2)
    - [No. 8], 1975-02-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0007; no show no. on slate; inferred as no. 8 based on date (Box 1)
    - No. 9, 1975-03-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0008 (Box 1)
    - No. 10, 1975-03-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0009 (Box 2)
    - No. 11, 1975-03-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0010 (Box 2)
    - [No. 12], 1975-03-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0011 (Box 2)
    - No. 13, 1975-04-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0012 (Box 2)
    - No. 14, 1975-04-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0013 (Box 2)
    - No. 15, 1975-04-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0014 (Box 2)
    - No. 16, 1975-04-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0016; originally misidentified as episode 17 (Box 2)
    - No. 17, 1975-05-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0017; originally misidentified as episode 18 (Box 2)
    - No. 19, 1975-05-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0018 (Box 2)
    - No. 20, 1975-05-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0019 (Box 3)
    - [No. 21], 1975-05-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0020 (Box 3)
    - No. 22, 1975-05-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0021 (Box 3)
    - No. 23, 1975-06-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0022 (Box 3)
    - No. 24, 1975-06-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0023 (Box 3)
    - No. 25, 1975-06-19; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0024 (Box 3)
    - No. 26, 1975-06-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0025 (Box 3)
    - [No. 27], 1975-07-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0026 (Box 3)
    - No. 28, 1975-07-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0027 (Box 3)
    - No. 201, 1975-09-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0028 (Box 4)
    - No. 202, 1975-09-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0029 (Box 4)
    - No. 203, 1975-09-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0030 (Box 4)
    - No. 204, 1975-09-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0031 (Box 4)
    - No. 205, 1975-10-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0032 (Box 4)
    - No. 206, 1975-10-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0033 (Box 4)
    - No. 207, 1975-10-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0034 (Box 4)
    - No. 208, 1975-10-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0035 (Box 4)
    - No. 209, 1975-10-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0036 (Box 4)
    - No. 210, 1975-11-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0037 (Box 5)
    - No. 211, 1975-11-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0038 (Box 5)
    - No. 212, 1975-11-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0039 (Box 5)
    - No. 213, 1975-11-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0040 (Box 5)
    - No. 214, 1975-12-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0041 (Box 5)
    - No. 215, 1975-12-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0042 (Box 5)
    - No. 216, 1975-12-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0043 (Box 5)
    - No. 217, 1975-12-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0044 (Box 5)
  - Videorecordings, 1976
    - No. 218, 1976-01-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0045 (Box 5)
    - No. 219, 1976-01-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0046 (Box 5)
    - No. 220, 1976-01-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0047 (Box 6)
    - No. 221, 1976-01-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0048 (Box 6)
    - No. 222, 1976-01-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0049 (Box 6)
    - No. 223, 1976-02-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0050 (Box 6)
    - No. 224, 1976-02-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0051 (Box 6)
    - No. 225, 1976-02-19; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0052 (Box 6)
    - No. 226, 1976-02-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0053 (Box 6)
    - No. 227, 1976-03-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0054 (Box 6)
    - No. 228, 1976-03-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0055 (Box 6)
    - No. 229, 1976-03-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0056 (Box 7)
    - No. 230, 1976-03-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0057 (Box 7)
    - No. 231, 1976-04-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0058 (Box 7)
    - No. 232, 1976-04-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0059 (Box 7)
    - No. 233, 1976-04-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0060 (Box 7)
    - No. 234, 1976-04-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0061 (Box 7)
    - No. 235, 1976-05-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0062 (Box 7)
    - No. 236, 1976-05-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0063 (Box 7)
    - No. 237, 1976-05-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0064 (Box 7)
    - No. 239, 1976-05-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0065 (Box 8)
    - No. 241, 1976-06-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0066 (Box 8)
    - No. 242, 1976-06-19; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0067 (Box 8)
    - No. 243, 1976-06-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0068 (Box 8)
    - No. 301, 1976-07-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0069; slate mislabels show as episode 244 (this is episode 301) (Box 8)
    - No. 302, 1976-07-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0070 (Box 8)
    - No. 303, 1976-07-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0071 (Box 8)
    - No. 304, 1976-07-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0072 (Box 8)
    - No. 309, 1976-08-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0073 (Box 8)
    - No. 310, 1976-09-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0074 (Box 9)
    - No. 311, 1976-09-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0075 (Box 9)
    - No. 312, 1976-09-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0076 (Box 9)
    - No. 313, 1976-09-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0077 (Box 9)
    - No. 314, 1976-10-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0078 (Box 9)
    - No. 315, 1976-10-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0079 (Box 9)
    - No. 316, 1976-10-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0080 (Box 9)
    - No. 317, 1976-10-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0081 (Box 9)
    - No. 322, 1976-11-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0082 (Box 9)
    - No. 323, 1976-12-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0083 (Box 10)
    - No. 324, 1976-12-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0084 (Box 10)
    - No. 325, 1976-12-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0085 (Box 10)
    - No. 326, 1976-12-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0086 (Box 10)
    - No. 327, 1976-12-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0087 (Box 10)
  - Videorecordings, 1977
    - No. 328, 1977-01-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0088 (Box 10)
    - No. 329, 1977-01-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0089 (Box 10)
    - No. 330, 1977-01-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0090 (Box 10)
    - No. 331, 1977-01-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0091 (Box 10)
    - No. 332, 1977-02-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0092 (Box 11)
    - No. 333, 1977-02-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0093 (Box 11)
    - No. 334, 1977-02-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0094 (Box 11)
    - No. 335, 1977-02-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0095 (Box 11)
    - No. 336, 1977-03-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0096 (Box 11)
    - No. 337, 1977-03-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0097 (Box 11)
    - No. 338, 1977-03-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0098 (Box 11)
    - No. 339, 1977-03-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0099 (Box 11)
    - No. 340, 1977-03-31; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0100 (Box 11)
    - No. 341, 1977-04-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0101 (Box 12)
    - No. 342, 1977-04-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0102 (Box 12)
    - No. 343, 1977-04-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0103 (Box 12)
    - No. 344, 1977-04-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0104 (Box 12)
    - No. 345, 1977-05-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0105 (Box 12)
    - No. 346, 1977-05-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0106 (Box 12)
    - No. 350, 1977-06-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0107 (Box 12)
    - No. 351, 1977-06-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0108 (Box 12)
    - No. 352, 1977-06-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0109 (Box 12)
    - No. 401, 1977-06-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0110 (Box 13)
    - No. 402, 1977-07-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0111 (Box 13)
    - No. 403, 1977-07-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0112 (Box 13)
    - No. 404, 1977-07-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0113 (Box 13)
    - No. 405, 1977-07-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0114 (Box 13)
    - No. 406, 1977-08-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0115 (Box 13)
    - No. 407, 1977-08-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0116 (Box 13)
    - No. 408, 1977-08-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0117 (Box 13)
    - No. 409, 1977-08-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0118 (Box 13)
    - No. 410, 1977-09-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0119 (Box 14)
    - No. 411, 1977-09-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0120 (Box 14)
    - No. 412, 1977-09-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0121 (Box 14)
    - No. 413, 1977-09-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0122 (Box 14)
    - No. 414, 1977-09-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0123 (Box 14)
    - No. 415, 1977-10-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0124 (Box 14)
    - No. 416, 1977-10-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0125 (Box 14)
    - No. 417, 1977-10-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0126 (Box 14)
    - No. 418, 1977-10-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0127 (Box 14)
    - No. 419, 1977-11-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0128 (Box 15)
    - No. 420, 1977-11-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0129 (Box 15)
    - No. 421, 1977-11-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0130 (Box 15)
    - No. 422, 1977-11-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0131 (Box 15)
    - No. 423, 1977-12-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0132 (Box 15)
    - No. 424, 1977-12-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0133 (Box 15)
    - No. 425, 1977-12-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0134 (Box 15)
    - No. 426, 1977-12-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0135 (Box 15)
    - No. 427, 1977-12-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0136 (Box 15)
  - Videorecordings, 1978
    - No. 428, 1978-01-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0137 (Box 16)
    - No. 429, 1978-01-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0138 (Box 16)
    - No. 430, 1978-01-19; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0139 (Box 16)
    - No. 431, 1978-01-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0140 (Box 16)
    - No. 432, 1978-02-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0141 (Box 16)
    - No. 433, 1978-02-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0142 (Box 16)
    - No. 434, 1978-02-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0143 (Box 16)
    - No. 435, 1978-02-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0144 (Box 16)
    - No. 436, 1978-03-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0145 (Box 16)
    - No. 437, 1978-03-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0146 (Box 17)
    - No. 438, 1978-03-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0147 (Box 17)
    - No. 439, 1978-03-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0148 (Box 17)
    - No. 440, 1978-03-31; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0149 (Box 17)
    - No. 441, 1978-04-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0150 (Box 17)
    - No. 442, 1978-04-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0151 (Box 17)
    - No. 443, 1978-04-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0153 (Box 17)
    - No. 444, 1978-04-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0154 (Box 17)